<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blog on ADRW</title>
    <link>https://adrwh.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blog on ADRW</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://adrwh.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup Ansible on your Mac to connect to remote Windows Domain Servers/Workstations using secure Kerberos</title>
      <link>https://adrwh.github.io/blog/ansible-macos-kerberos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adrwh.github.io/blog/ansible-macos-kerberos/</guid>
      <description>This article shows you how to setup Ansible on your Mac to connect to remote Windows Domain Servers/Workstations using secure Kerberos.
Ansible supports authentication to Windows using NTLM over http (bad), NTLM over https (better) our Kerberos over HTTPS (best). Surprisingly it&#39;s the easiest to setup also, so no excuses.
We&#39;re going to cover the following setup requirements.
 Installing Pywinrm  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating Watchers in Elasticsearch to catch Domain Admin security group changes</title>
      <link>https://adrwh.github.io/blog/elastic-watchers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 21:27:54 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adrwh.github.io/blog/elastic-watchers/</guid>
      <description>We are going to setup an alert for whenever our Domain Admin group is changed. This is great for security context as well as general auditing.
 Please note: This is not a defender safeguard to detect privilege escalation. Smart attackers will not be adding themselves to the Domain Admin group.
 First create your search using Kibana. In this example i am going to search for changes to the Domain Admins security group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MS Teams Channel Conversation &#34;Backup&#34;</title>
      <link>https://adrwh.github.io/blog/msteams-backup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 15:38:04 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adrwh.github.io/blog/msteams-backup/</guid>
      <description>We use Microsoft Teams, and probably as most, create a new team when it was first released, however have now decided to move to a new Team. This is all fine, but when we went looking for a &amp;ldquo;migration&amp;rdquo; pathway, there wasn&#39;t one. Instead we settled on making a backup/copy for historical purposes.
I went searching PowerShell for cmdlets to &amp;ldquo;backup&amp;rdquo; Teams and didn&#39;t find any. I then went searching the Microsoft Graph API and found the Teams API resources.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>