<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ansible on ADRW</title>
    <link>https://adrwh.github.io/tags/ansible/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ansible on ADRW</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://adrwh.github.io/tags/ansible/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Using ansible to post MS Teams messages</title>
      <link>https://adrwh.github.io/blog/ansible-api-post-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adrwh.github.io/blog/ansible-api-post-teams/</guid>
      <description>In this post i&#39;ll show you one way you can interact with Microsoft Teams (or any API) in your ansible playbooks. The idea behind doing this was initially to provide a simple way to log progress from the command line, seeing as thats where they already spend a lot of time, but obviously there are many use cases for something like this. Maybe you want your playbook to interact with other messaging APIs while it runs, or send progress updates to other team members etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup Ansible on your Mac to connect to remote Windows Domain Servers/Workstations using secure Kerberos</title>
      <link>https://adrwh.github.io/blog/ansible-macos-kerberos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adrwh.github.io/blog/ansible-macos-kerberos/</guid>
      <description>Ansible supports authentication to Windows using NTLM over http (bad), NTLM over https (better) or Kerberos over HTTPS (best). Surprisingly it&#39;s the easiest to setup also, so no excuses. Ansible&#39;s documentation states that if your running in a domain environment, Kerberos should be used over NTLM.
We&#39;re going to cover the following setup requirements, then we will throw a couple commands at Windows to prove we have successfully authed.
Installing the requirements As i said, Kerberos is already installed on your Mac, so we just need to install the python winrm library.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>